Specialized vehicles such as aerial work platforms and ladder trucks
are typically used for low-speed driving and short-distance trips
they are primarily operated at low speeds and over short distances,
and all work is performed while the vehicle is stationary,
work time accounts for approximately 55% or more of the total operating time.
Fuel consumption resulting from the engine running while stationary
accounts for approximately 38% of total fuel consumption,
resulting in economic losses as well as emissions
exhaust fumes and noise emitted around the worksite.
To address these issues, ROC Auto Systems has
reusing high-voltage batteries from electric vehicles and drive systems from hybrid vehicles
to develop the e-PTO system, which electrifies aerial work platforms.
To this end, we conducted performance verification on the reused components.
The results of the performance verification for the hybrid vehicle drive system
Despite the power drive converter having reached the end of its service life,
it was found that there was no performance degradation.
Next are the performance verification results for the electric vehicle’s high-voltage battery,
which showed that performance was maintained at approximately 80% or higher compared to a new battery.
To electrify aerial work platforms, we have independently developed an e-PTO Control Unit and
a Motor Control Unit.
In addition, along with the drive motor and inverter—which are reused components from hybrid vehicles—
the e-PTO Control Unit and the e-PTO hydraulic pump,
into a single package to improve installability and serviceability.
In addition, for the high-voltage battery—a reusable component from electric vehicles—
we developed a casing to improve cooling performance and protect the battery, and
and is equipped with a charging system that includes an On-Board Charger
and a charging port to support slow charging.
ROC Auto System’s electrified vehicles
can be charged via a standard slow-charging plug, just like conventional electric vehicles, and
the electrification of ROC Auto System’s e-PTO system
can save approximately 1,300 liters of fuel per year,
resulting in greenhouse gas emissions reductions of approximately 3.5 tons.